Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Campers files 1925-1967
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1935
      - Steubing, William (1935-1936) (Box 7)
      - Stone, Wade (Box 7)
      - Storer, James (Box 7)
      - Taylor, Brice (1935-1936) (deceased 11/29/1941) (Box 7)
      - Thompson, Bradley (1935-1936) (Box 7)
      - Twining, Herbert Harrison (Bud) (Box 7)
      - Vaile, Richard (1935-1936) (Box 8)
      - Van Dusen, Charles (Box 8)
      - Welker, John (Box 8)
      - Wheelock, John (1935-1936) (Box 8)
      - Whiting, Macauley (1935-1936) (Box 8)
      - Wiltse, Dean (includes John) (Box 8)
    - 1936
      [Restricted until January 1 2036 ]
      - Medical Records (Box 8)
      - Alison, Denis (Spike) (Box 8)
      - Alison, David (includes Tom) (Box 8)
      - Ballard, Tom (Box 8)
      - Bartemeier, John Albert (Box 8)
      - Bear, Tom (Box 8)
      - Bissell, John (Box 8)
      - Bonisteel, Roscoe O., Jr. (Bud) (Box 8)
      - Brown, Michael (Mike) (Box 8)
      - Brown, Tom (Box 8)
      - Carrel, George (Box 8)
      - Carruthers, Edward (Box 8)
      - Cottrell, Henry (Box 8)
      - Dillon, Robert (Box 8)
      - Dock, Robert (Box 8)
      - Edmonson, Don (Box 8)
      - Edwards, J. William (Box 8)
      - Edwards, Joseph (Box 8)
      - Emmert, Bruce (Box 8)
      - Finley, Robert (Box 8)
      - Fletcher, Charles (Box 8)
      - Gault, David (Box 8)
      - Geier, Eugene (Box 8)
      - Goldberg, Edward (Box 8)
      - Higbie, Charles (Box 8)
      - Hurlbut, Philip (Box 8)
      - Jeffrey, Steven (Box 8)
      - Lighthall, Billie (Box 8)
      - Limback, Paul (Box 8)
      - Lord, James (Box 8)
      - Lorenzen, Robert (Box 8)
      - MacGrellish, William H. (Box 8)
      - Moxley, Scott (includes David) (Box 8)
      - Paul, Jack (Box 8)
      - Platt, Henry (Box 8)
      - Reichhold, Dieter (Box 8)
      - Rice, Dan (Box 8)
      - Rorick, Marvin (1936-1937) (Box 8)
      - Spreng, Warren (see also Dick Spreng) (Box 8)
      - Stason, Blythe (Box 8)
      - Storer, Peter (Box 8)
      - Storrs, Philip (includes Al) (Box 8)
      - Thomas, Robert (Box 8)
      - Whiting, Henry (Box 8)
      - Wilson, Erwin (Box 8)
      - Wulsen, Tom (Box 8)
    - 1937
      [Restricted until January 1 2037 ]
      - Alvary, Leon, Jr. (Box 8)
      - Bement, Roberts Edwin, Jr. (Box 8)
      - Booth, Stephen (includes David) (Box 8)
      - Brunner, Toby (Box 8)
      - Buhrman, Peter (Box 8)
      - Carney, John E. (Box 8)
      - Carrick, C. William (Box 8)
      - Couzens, Frank, Jr. (Box 8)
      - Couzens, James (Box 8)
      - Duryea, F. Charles, Jr. (Box 8)
      - Fechheimer, Nate (Box 8)
      - Foley, William R. (Box 8)
      - Frey, John (Box 8)
      - Gardner, John (Box 8)
      - Gates, Dick (Box 8)
      - Geier, Otto (Box 8)
      - Griffith, William C., Jr. (Box 8)
      - Hildreth, Owen (Box 8)
      - Johnson, Frederick D. (Box 8)
      - Johnson, Harold (Box 8)
      - Low, Stephen (Box 8)
      - Mackenzie, Robert D., Jr. (Box 8)
      - Marshall, Dr. & Mrs. Mark (Box 8)
      - McIlwraith, John Gray (Box 9)
      - Murphy, John (Box 9)
      - Neave, Harold E., Jr. (Buzzie) (Box 9)
      - Pattengill, H. Richard (Box 9)
      - Saunders, Billie (see Gordon Saunders-Box 7) (Box 9)
      - Shaffer, Frederic S., Jr. (Box 9)
      - Sommer, Benjamin L. (includes Thomas P.) (Box 9)
      - Sperry, Donald D., Jr. (Box 9)
      - Terry, Paul B. (Box 9)
      - Wintringer, Robert L., Jr. (Box 9)
      - Woods, James Park, Jr. (Box 9)
      - Wuerfel, Robert D. (Box 9)
    - 1938
      [Restricted until January 1 2038 ]
      - Allen, Ross Lorraine, Jr. (Box 9)
      - Bopp, Andrew Richard (Box 9)
      - Cook, John Barth (Box 9)
      - Galster, John Frederic (Box 9)
      - Long, Samuel Spreng (Box 9)
      - Lyman, William H. (Box 9)
      - Peirsol, John Michael (Box 9)
      - Peirsol, Thomas Reardon (Box 9)
      - Rorick, Richard P. (Box 9)
      - Rorick, Robert Baker (Box 9)
      - Shuell, John M. (Box 9)
      - Simmons, Warren (Box 9)
      - Zeder, James Churchill (Box 9)
    - 1939
      [Restricted until January 1 2039 ]
      - Clifford, Churchill (includes Frederick) (Box 9)
      - Eden, Johnny (Box 9)
      - Garred, Thomas Arthur (Box 9)
      - Gorrell, Edgar S. (Peter) (Box 9)
      - Hare, Lauren Clark (Larry) (Box 9)
      - Knoroles, Jimmie (Box 9)
      - Lauver, Andrew Donald (Andy) (Box 9)
      - McPherson, Paul S. (includes Duncan and Rene) (Box 9)
      - Middleton, Blake (Box 9)
      - Monteith, Jimmy (Box 9)
      - Moore, Tommy (Box 9)
      - Penberthy, John (1939-1942) (Box 9)
      - Purcell, Bradford Moore (Box 9)
      - Tucker, David A. (Box 9)
    - 1940
      [Restricted until January 1 2040 ]
      - Baker, Russell (Box 9)
      - Barr, John (Box 9)
      - Brumbach, William P., Jr. (Box 9)
      - Case, Fred S. (Box 9)
      - Dye, John Van Ausdal (Box 9)
      - Hall, Bill (Box 9)
      - Hall, Joe (Box 9)
      - Hodges, James (Box 9)
      - Jordan, James (Box 9)
      - Jordan, Jerry H. (includes John) (Box 9)
      - Kretzschmar, Bill (Box 9)
      - Nehil, Thomas E. (Box 9)
      - Oakman, Charles Robert (Box 9)
      - Ruckelshaus, Jack (Box 9)
      - Slocum, Larry (Box 9)
      - Swainsons, Jillson [empty] (Box 9)
      - Thomas, John (Box 9)
      - Thompson, Tommy (Box 9)
      - Valade, Bob (Box 9)
      - Whiting, Peter (Box 9)
    - 1941
      [Restricted until January 1 2041 ]
      - Bartrop, James Jerome (Jerry) (1941-1942) (Box 9)
      - Bates, William O., III (Bill) (Box 9)
      - Bowen, Peter Francis (Box 9)
      - Brady, Peter (Box 9)
      - Duryea, Dick (Box 9)
      - Miller, Edward Kingsford (Ted) (Box 9)
      - Muirhead, Stanley N., Jr. (Box 9)
      - Packard, Charles E. (Box 9)
      - Reeves, Robert (includes John & Michael) (Box 9)
      - Robinson, Joseph L. (Joey) (Box 9)
      - Stroh, Eric Wetherill (Box 9)
      - Tucker, Randolph (Ranny) (Box 9)
      - Whitsell, Douglas S. (1941-1943) (Box 9)
      - Williams, Lawrence B. (1941-1942) (Box 9)
      - Willis, David Pearce (Dave) (Box 9)
      - Windisch, R. Humphrey (Box 9)
    - 1942
      [Restricted until January 1 2042 ]
      - Barton, Joseph Leonard (Box 10)
      - Brown, A. J. Terry, Jr. (Box 10)
      - Brown, William W. (Box 10)
      - Cook, Addison Porter (Box 10)
      - Duncan, Raymond (Box 10)
      - Funk, William Irvin G. (Bill) (Box 10)
      - Ganiard, Roderick F. (Box 10)
      - Genebach, Carleton (Skip) G. (Box 10)
      - Gutchess, Allen D., Jr. (Box 10)
      - Hendrie, Joseph M. (Joe) (Box 10)
      - Kretchmar, James Lauren (Box 10)
      - Leonard, Norman Harold (Box 10)
      - Lund, Bruce Reid (Box 10)
      - Malcolm, Karl Day (Box 10)
      - Morris, Frank Rockwell, Jr. (Box 10)
      - Nebel, Richard (Box 10)
      - Parsons, Donald Robert (Box 10)
      - Remien, Herbert Campbell (Box 10)
      - Sheets, Joseph Louis (Box 10)
      - Schwartz, Frank George (Box 10)
      - Spencer, Peter (Box 10)
      - Wagner, Robert Joel (Box 10)
    - 1943
      [Restricted until January 1 2043 ]
      - Andrews, Douglas W. (Box 10)
      - Andrews, Harold P. (Box 10)
      - Beamer, Jim Franklin (Box 10)
      - Betz, Roscoe, Jr. (Box 10)
      - Calhoon, Jack F. (Box 10)
      - Carrick, Bud (Box 10)
      - Desenberg, Charles M. (Box 10)
      - Desenberg, Milford M. (Box 10)
      - DeVilbis, Thomas Alexander (Box 10)
      - Field, Burke Rayner (includes Clarke Hills) (Box 10)
      - Ford, Mark (Box 10)
      - Hamilton, Schuyler (Box 10)
      - Hoffman, Peter Jay (Box 10)
      - Molloy, Peter H. (Box 10)
      - Montgomery, William Edward (Box 10)
      - O'Rourke, James (Box 10)
      - Pheatt, James Henry, III (Box 10)
      - Schulz, Paul Henry (Box 10)
      - Stranahan, Stephen (Box 10)
      - Walz, William Ludwig, Jr. (Box 10)
      - Yarnell, Joseph (Box 10)
    - 1944
      [Restricted until January 1 2044 ]
      - Barclay, Charles J. (Jerry) (Box 10)
      - Belote, James M. (Box 10)
      - Bennett, Kingsley (Box 10)
      - Beresford, John Booth (Box 10)
      - Biddle, John J. (Box 10)
      - Blanchard, Robert Edgar (Box 10)
      - Bleekman, Buzzie (Box 10)
      - Bowes, David Bigelow (Box 10)
      - Branion, Michael H. C. (Box 10)
      - Britner, Richard B. (Box 10)
      - Brown, Peter Truman (Box 10)
      - Bryant, John Arthur (Box 10)
      - Butterfield, Anthony Swindt (Box 10)
      - Craft, Robert David (Box 10)
      - Custer, Henry Jr. (Box 10)
      - Deacon, Richard W. (Box 10)
      - Dennison, David Severin (Box 10)
      - Dethmers, J. Robert (Box 10)
      - Drake, Robert Lincoln (Box 10)
      - Ettinger, Adrian Jr. (Box 10)
      - Farley, William David (Bill) (Box 10)
      - Fink, Peter Rupert (Box 10)
      - Foley, Norman K., Jr. (Box 10)
      - Ford, Robert Frazer (Box 10)
      - Frost, Albert C. (Box 10)
      - Frye, Carl Marvin (Box 10)
      - Garmey, Stephen (Box 10)
      - Hammond, James Warren (Box 10)
      - Hammond, Thomas Whipple (Box 10)
      - Hancock, David Alan (Box 10)
      - Handley, Edward William (Box 10)
      - Harris, John Bradley (includes David) (Box 10)
      - Hawley, Thomas Gardner III (Box 10)
      - Henning, A. Farnam (Box 10)
      - Herbert, William James (Box 10)
      - Hickham, Robert Thomas (Box 10)
      - Higbie, David Wing (Box 10)
      - Hill, David Gower (Box 10)
      - Hodges, John Barnett (Box 10)
      - Johnson, Richard Charles (Box 10)
      - Kaump, Donald Hunter (includes Robert & Jack) (Box 10)
      - Kurcz, Jerome (includes Robert) (Box 10)
      - Lanning, Walter Lon (Box 10)
      - Mac Rae, Robert Eugene (Box 10)
      - McCaffree, Charles (includes David) (Box 10)
      - McIntyre, Robert James (Box 10)
      - Morse, Peter (Box 10)
      - Ogilvie, James Donald (Box 10)
      - Parker, Alden Russell (Box 10)
      - Philbin, Patrick William (Box 10)
      - Rentschler, J. F. (Jeff) (1944-1949) (Box 10)
      - Rice, James Stanford (Box 10)
      - Riecker, John Ernest (includes James Charles) (Box 10)
      - Risk, Paul H., Jr. (Box 10)
      - Schruben, Ronald Lee (Box 10)
      - Shehan, James Phillip (Box 10)
      - Shelden, Henry D. (Box 10)
      - Sherer, Sam (Box 10)
      - Sikarovsky, Edmond Lee (Box 10)
      - Sloan, Malachi W., III (Box 10)
      - Stason, William Boaz (Box 10)
      - Stevens, William Frederic (Box 10)
      - Struever, Stuart McKee (Box 10)
      - Tallman, Edward R. (Box 10)
      - Taylor, James Morrison, Jr. (Box 10)
      - Tripp, William S. (Billy) (Box 10)
      - Van Alstyne, Johnnie (Box 10)
      - Volpe, Stanley L. (Box 10)
      - Walker, Harry Edward (Box 10)
      - Willey, Edward Norburn (Box 10)
      - Wilson, Donald Ralph (Box 10)
    - 1945
      [Restricted until January 1 2045 ]
      - Addison, James III (Box 11)
      - Albrecht, Frederick Robert (Box 11)
      - Barrett, Bill (Box 11)
      - Batsch, Frank W. (Box 11)
      - Beck, Frederick Walter (Box 11)
      - Beebe, Robert Alan (Box 11)
      - Benz, Robert Raymond (Box 11)
      - Bicknell, John Mark (Box 11)
      - Blach, Harold B., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Black, George Gilcrest (Box 11)
      - Bliss, Robert A. (Box 11)
      - Borgerson, Keith (Box 11)
      - Bradfield, John Jr. (Box 11)
      - Bushong, Ben (Box 11)
      - Butler, Edward Enwright, Jr. (Box 11)
      - Butt, Harold Luther (Box 11)
      - Caulkins, Henry Lewis II (Box 11)
      - Chase, William Byer II (Box 11)
      - Chevrie, Michael Manning (includes Owen James) (Box 11)
      - Collins, Donald Grant (Box 11)
      - Cooper, Robert J., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Darling, Gary Cyrenus Garrett III (includes David Payne) (Box 11)
      - Douglas, Robert Hugh (Box 11)
      - Foster, Hugh Mason, Jr. (Box 11)
      - Frye, Richard Emerson (Box 11)
      - Furman, Sherwood Murray (Woody) (Box 11)
      - Fuss, Robert Carson (Box 11)
      - Gelb, Thomas Alfred (Box 11)
      - Ginn, John Curtiss (Box 11)
      - Goetz, Angus Gerald, Jr. (Jerry) (Box 11)
      - Haman, Arthur Charles (Box 11)
      - Hoexter, Robert Henry (Box 11)
      - Holt, W. Stanley, Jr. (Box 11)
      - Hubbard, James Alfred (1945-1946) (Box 11)
      - Johnson, Richard D. (Box 11)
      - Jones, Samuel M. III (Box 11)
      - Kelter, Don L. (Box 11)
      - Kessel, William W. (Box 11)
      - Kidder, Laurence E. (Box 11)
      - Kressmann, Jacques (Box 11)
      - Lammert, Warren B., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Lathrop, Robert Curtiss (Box 11)
      - Lodish, Michael (Box 11)
      - Long, Theodore Dixon (Box 11)
      - Lorre, Dean Hendrickson (Box 11)
      - Ludington, Martin Lammert (Box 11)
      - Macauley, Edward Alvan (Box 11)
      - Martin, Richard H. (Box 11)
      - McConnell, Thomas Royce (Box 11)
      - Meland, Richard Denny (Box 11)
      - Mitchell, Irving Stuart (Box 11)
      - Moss, David Francis (Box 11)
      - Niehuss, John Marvin (Box 11)
      - Painter, Don Charles (Box 11)
      - Perry, Clair (Box 11)
      - Reindel, George John III (Box 11)
      - Rickert, Herbert Elvin (Box 11)
      - Roscoe, Richard Powell (Box 11)
      - Sherman, George Wilson (Joe) (Box 11)
      - Sisson, Edward Brunck (Box 11)
      - Skillman, Harry (Butch) (Box 11)
      - Stowe, Frederick Taylor II (Box 11)
      - Tann, Donald Wittman (Box 11)
      - Taylor, John Ripley (Box 11)
      - Villerot, George E. (Box 11)
      - Volpe, Salvatore (Box 11)
      - Wensinger, Charles Franklin (Box 11)
      - Williamson, Richard Lee (Box 11)
      - Willson, Jay Curtis (Box 11)
      - Wiseman, Thomas Wetzler, Jr. (Box 11)
    - 1946
      [Restricted until January 1 2046 ]
      - Adcock, Howard (Box 11)
      - Atkins, Thomas M. (Box 11)
      - Bailey, Edmond I. (Box 11)
      - Barnard, Hugh Neil (Box 11)
      - Beardsley, Robert Buchanan (Box 11)
      - Buhl, Larry (Box 11)
      - Cameron, Robert Bruce (Box 11)
      - Cook, George S. (Box 11)
      - Couper, Thomas Edward (Box 11)
      - Cushing, James B. (Box 11)
      - Fauster, John (Jack) (Box 11)
      - Ficks, Lee B. (Box 11)
      - Flourney, Lev. Jr. (Box 11)
      - Freeland, John (Box 11)
      - Glover, George H., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Goetz, Albert G., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Gounsley, Dennis E. (Box 11)
      - Healey, Tony (1946-1947) (Box 11)
      - Kleis, John C. (Box 11)
      - Lashmet, Michael H. (1946-1947) (Box 11)
      - Machus, Robert (Box 11)
      - Maxwell, J. Robert (Box 11)
      - McManus, Jimmy (Box 11)
      - Reinert, Owen (Staff 1946) (Box 11)
    - 1947
      [Restricted until January 1 2047 ]
      - Anderson, Marc B. (Box 11)
      - Anderson, Frederich Reid (Box 11)
      - Avery, Frederick D., Jr. (Box 11)
      - Blake, Eugene (includes Peter) (Box 11)
      - Breuer, Walter (Box 11)
      - Buskirk, George (Box 11)
      - Domke, John Philip (Box 11)
      - Enck, Charles Francis (Box 11)
      - Fisher, Walter Briggs (Box 11)
      - Frendreis, Richard Joseph (Box 11)
      - Giannaris, James S. (Box 11)
      - Hickox, Charles Chatterton "Chat" (Box 11)
      - Kales, Robert Gray, Jr. (Box 11)
      - Kerr, Henry Hampton, III (Box 11)
      - Kersey, Robert Evans (Box 11)
      - Knaggs, Howard (Box 11)
      - Loebel, Andre Henri (Box 11)
      - Lynch, Jerry David (1947-1949) (Box 11)
      - Merseles, Craig Philip (Box 12)
      - Meyers, Gerson Ellis (Box 12)
      - Orwig, John Scott, Jr. (Scotty) (1947-1952) (Box 12)
      - Reynolds, C. Kelly, III (Box 12)
      - Server, David Lee (Bud) (1947-1949) (Box 12)
      - Stumb, Charles E. (includes William Thomas) (Box 12)
      - Thompson, Guy Bradley (Box 12)
      - Whyel, George L., Jr. (Box 12)
      - Will, Thomas Sherman (Tom) (1947-1949) (Box 12)
    - 1948
      [Restricted until January 1 2048 ]
      - Batdorff, Jack (Box 12)
      - Belknap, Charles Lewis (Chuck (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Benson, Rupert Hazelton (Box 12)
      - Bishop, Leonard James (Jimmie) (Box 12)
      - Burr, Henry (includes Walter) (Box 12)
      - Chidsey, Herbert Malott (Box 12)
      - Denham, Roger (Box 12)
      - Folger, Thomas K. (Box 12)
      - Gallogly, William George (Box 12)
      - Glancy, Alfred Robinson (Robin) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Graham, Robert J. (Bobby) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Hammond, Rudolph E. (includes Peter S.) (Box 12)
      - Healey, Graham (Box 12)
      - Jones, Parry (Box 12)
      - Kaine, Lawrence Francis (Box 12)
      - Keyes, Ralph Clark, Jr. (Box 12)
      - LeRoy, Robert Bradford (Bob) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Lippincott, Dallas (includes Charles) (Box 12)
      - Pence, John Leavitt (Pete) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Thrasher, Steven Duane (Steve) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
    - 1949
      [Restricted until January 1 2049 ]
      - Betz, Frederic (Fritz) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Bokhof, Henry Steel, Jr. (includes Dick & Ted) (1949-1950) (Box 12)
      - Burton, Paul Leonard, Jr. (Box 12)
      - Byrne, Dan (Danno) (Box 12)
      - Cashman, John Henry (Jack) (1946-1949) (Box 12)
      - Clark, Lindley Edward, Jr. (Eddie) (Box 12)
      - Cook, Richard M. (Cookie) (Box 12)
      - Cooper, Forster (includes John Robert) (Box 12)
      - Creden, John T. (Jack) (Box 12)
      - Crosier, Ray (Box 12)
      - Cummings, Thomas Frederick (Tom) (Box 12)
      - de Koning, Kendrik John (Kim) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - DeVilbiss, James Bond (Jim) (Box 12)
      - Dinan, John T., Jr. (Box 12)
      - Dudley, William Taber (Bill) (Box 12)
      - Dunin, Stanley Edward (Stas) (Box 12)
      - Falconer, Robert Daniels (Bobby) (Box 12)
      - Fentress, James Francis, Jr. (Jim) (Box 12)
      - Fletcher, Ralph G. (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Foley, John Russell (Box 12)
      - Gausewitz, Karl (Box 12)
      - Geller, Peter Tolman (Pete) (includes Michael Daniel) (1949-1950) (Box 12)
      - Griffin, William Joseph, Jr. (Bill) (includes Hollis & Roger) (1949-1953) (Box 12)
      - Haass, Frederick (Fritz) (Box 12)
      - Hyde, Andrew Cornwall (Andy) (includes Fritz) (Box 12)
      - Johnston, Donald Byrne (Don) (includes Bill) (1949-1955) (Box 12)
      - Johnston, James Clarke, Jr. (Jimmy) (Box 12)
      - Kearney, Stephen W. (Steve) (Box 12)
      - Keen, Charles Willard, III (Bubby) (Box 12)
      - Kendrick, Ben Joseph (Ben) (Box 12)
      - Klores, Stanley Whitehouse (Stan) (Box 12)
      - McMillin, Robert Edward (Bob) (Box 12)
      - Marks, David Owen (Dave) (Box 12)
      - Martin, Gary Schatz (Butch) (Box 12)
      - Martin, Patrick M. (Pat) (1949-1950) (Box 12)
      - Morgan, Philip Smith (Phil) (1946-1949) (Box 12)
      - Morton, James Townsend (Jimmy) (Box 12)
      - Pollock, Frank Gordon (Frank) (Box 12)
      - Potter, Doran Peter (Box 12)
      - Richardson, David Riley (Box 12)
      - Ridley, (Robert) Roy (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Rovner, David Mark (Box 12)
      - Russell, William S. (Bill) (Box 12)
      - Schultz, Paul Herbert (Box 12)
      - Smith, Michael J. (Mike) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Smith, Rayburn Ross (Ross) (Box 12)
      - Taylor, Thomas W. (Box 12)
      - Tope, Harry Earle (Earle) (Box 13)
      - Wade, Morrison Theodore (Ted) (Box 13)
      - Weis, Thomas Thedieck (Tom) (Box 13)
      - Wheeler, William Truesdale (Trues) (Box 13)
      - Wiese, Joseph Frederic, Jr. (Freddy) (Box 13)
      - Williamson, George H. (Box 13)
      - Wolf, David Robert (Dave) (1945-1949) (Box 13)
      - Zybell, Bert William (Billy) (1948-1949) (Box 13)
    - 1950
      [Restricted until January 1 2050 ]
      - Affleck, William C. (Bill) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Allen, Jim (Box 13)
      - Appel, Kenny (Box 13)
      - Archangeli, Johnny (Box 13)
      - Baumgardner, Grant (Box 13)
      - Bixby, Charles D. (Danny) (1947 1948 1950) (Box 13)
      - Boehmer, Gustave (Box 13)
      - Brown, Donald Guerry (Don) (Box 13)
      - Caple, Al (Box 13)
      - Casaroll, Tony (Box 13)
      - Christy, Danny (Box 13)
      - Curby, Johnny (Box 13)
      - Dayton, Daniel Denison, Jr. (Danny) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Deibel, Dixie (Box 13)
      - DeGowin, Dick (1946 1950) (Box 13)
      - Drew, Tom [EMPTY] (Box 13)
      - Dungan, Al (includes Tom) (1950 1953) (Box 13)
      - Edgar, Pete (includes Mike) (Box 13)
      - Finton, Robert James (Bob) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Gove, Robert (Robbie) (Box 13)
      - Greenley, Don (Box 13)
      - Greenspan, Howard (Box 13)
      - Haynes, Harley (Box 13)
      - Hiebert, John (1945 1946, 1947 1950) (Box 13)
      - Horn, Steve (Box 13)
      - Hudson, Jeffery MacLaren (Jeff) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Jackson, John (Box 13)
      - Killian, Butch (Box 13)
      - King, Don (Box 13)
      - Kretchmar, Richard Herman (Dick) (Box 13)
      - LaCoe, Steve (Box 13)
      - Lavan, Martin Brian (Pat) (includes Sean Desmond) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Luckett, Pace (Box 13)
      - MacKinnon, Charles (Box 13)
      - MacLeod, William (Billy) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Mahoney, Jeremiah William (Jerry) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Marshall, John Waller (Johnny) (Box 13)
      - McEvoy, James (Jimmy) (Box 13)
      - Merritt, Buck (Box 13)
      - Miller, Duncan R. (Petie) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Montgomery, Mead (Box 13)
      - Nelson, Bob (Box 13)
      - Newstedt, George Edward (1949) (Box 13)
      - Outhwaite, Joe (Box 13)
      - Pemberton, Tom (Box 13)
      - Prentis, John (Box 13)
      - Ramsay, Dave (Box 13)
      - Schuler, Hans (includes Jim) (1953) (Box 13)
      - Score, Alvin (Box 13)
      - Sellers, Gary (Box 13)
      - Simmons, Ted (Box 13)
      - Singer, Dan (Box 13)
      - Sinz, Peter (Box 13)
      - Sullivan, Art (Box 13)
      - Webster, Pete (Box 13)
      - Wheelock, John C. (Box 13)
    - 1951
      [Restricted until January 1 2051 ]
      - Allen, John (includes Steve) (Box 14)
      - Backus, Mike (Box 14)
      - Berner, Bob (Box 14)
      - Brown, Robbie (includes Rickie) (Box 14)
      - Brust, Jack (Box 14)
      - Camara-Peon, Pat (Box 14)
      - Chambers, Rick (Box 14)
      - Colombo, Rickey (Box 14)
      - De Garmo, Pete (Box 14)
      - Denise, Doug (includes Dick and Jerry) (1951-1952) (Box 14)
      - Elliot, Charlie (includes Tom) (Box 14)
      - Eversman, Walt (Box 14)
      - Gallagher, Tim (Box 14)
      - Geitgey, Joe (Box 14)
      - Gilpin, Jim (Box 14)
      - Gittleman, Jimmy (Box 14)
      - Goes, Jose (includes Eduardo) (Box 14)
      - Gotz, Thomas Allan (Box 14)
      - Grant, Lex (Box 14)
      - Grass, Roger (Box 14)
      - Grinnell, Tom (Box 14)
      - Gugenheim, Bob (Box 14)
      - Haynes, Woody (Box 14)
      - Heinemann, Fred (Box 14)
      - Hodgson, Rich (Box 14)
      - Hogan, Jeff (includes Clem) (Box 14)
      - Holmes, Dave (Box 14)
      - Hughes, Ted (includes Robbie) (Box 14)
      - Hunter, Sandy (Box 14)
      - Kingsley, Tom (Box 14)
      - Koch-Weser, Peter (Box 14)
      - Kreimer, Tony (Box 14)
      - Larson, Walt (includes Clyde) (Box 14)
      - Lichty, Bill (Box 14)
      - Litow, Rickey (Box 14)
      - Marsh, Dave (Box 14)
      - Myers, Fritz (Box 14)
      - Niehuss, John (Box 14)
      - Norton, Chuck (Box 14)
      - Patterson, Dave (includes Don) (Box 14)
      - Pugh, Bill (Box 14)
      - Schnute, Bill (includes Carl and Jamie) (1951-1955) (Box 14)
      - Schweitzer, Bobby (Box 14)
      - Shine, Dan (Box 14)
      - Slayton, Butch (Box 14)
      - Sleight, John (Box 14)
      - Slezak, Dave (Box 14)
      - Smith, Hank (Box 14)
      - Smith, Butch (Box 14)
      - Spencer, Jack (Box 14)
      - Sprague, Jim (Box 14)
      - Stevens, Bill (Box 14)
      - Stewart, Sandy (includes Pete) (1950-1951) (Box 14)
      - Stewart, Tom (Box 14)
      - Thompson, Bill (Box 14)
      - Thompson, Johnny (Box 14)
      - Weiner, Vic (Box 14)
      - Welke, Bob (Box 14)
      - West, Johnny (Box 14)
      - White, Tom (Box 14)
      - Woolner, Bunny (Box 14)
      - Wright, Jay (Box 14)
      - Wright, Jim (Box 14)
    - 1952